Finding Aid for the National Hispanic Media Coalition Subject Files PASC.0278
UCLA Library Special Collections
National Hispanic Media Coalition subject files
circa 1982-circa 2000
UCLA Library Special Collections
National Hispanic Media Coalition
PASC.0278
19.5 Linear Feet (39 boxes and 1 shoe box)
The National Hispanic Media Coalition (NHMC)is a non profit organization formed to improve the image and employment of Hispanic Americans in all facets of the media industry and to advocate for media and telecommunications policies that benefit the Latino community. The collection consists of subject files documenting the NHMC's activities to address media-related issues affecting the Hispanic American community from ca. 1989 through 1999. Of particular note are files related to an ABC boycott organized by NHMC, NHMC's interest in media personality Howard Stern, material related to Univision/Hallmark and to the Disney company, as well as numerous petitions filed by NHMC with the Federal Communications Commission related to licenses or other business of radio and television stations nationwide.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9962185163606533
Biography
National Hispanic Media Coalition (NHMC), a non profit organization, was founded in Fall 1986. Originally the NHMC was formed as a coalition of community and professional groups to address a variety of media related issues affecting the Hispanic-American community across the county. The original office was established in Los Angeles, Calif. under the leadership of Armando Duron, Alex Nogales, and Esther Reneria. Over the years it has formed chapters in Albuquerque, Chicago, New York, San Antonio and other cities in the United States.
The organization endeavors to improve the image and employment of Hispanic Americans in all facets of the media industry and to advocate for media and telecommunications policies that benefit the Latino community. NHMC works locally and nationally to ensure the media industry takes responsibility for diversity and positive portrayals of all minorities in their daily operations. Since their inception the organization has maintained close contact with radio, television, motion picture, and newspaper industries, filed numerous petitions with the Federal Communications Commission to deny the licenses of radio and television stations nationwide, led grassroots demonstrations across the country, and held regular press conferences calling attention to issues and events at hand, among many other activities.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of subject files created by and documenting the National Hispanic Media Coalition's (NHMC) activities to address media-related issues affecting the Hispanic American community from ca. 1989 through 1999. The bulk of the files contain information about various organizations, people, and events and include a mixture of original and photocopied clippings, occasional research notes, press releases, and ephemera. Additionally, there may be occasional legal documents, FCC filings, correspondence and a small amount of incomplete meeting agendas and notes for NHMC Board of Directors and/or Steering Committee meetings. Of particular note are files related to an ABC boycott organized by NHMC, NHMC's interest in media personality Howard Stern, material related to Univision/Hallmark and to the Disney company, and numerous petitions filed by NHMC with the Federal Communications Commission related to licenses or other business of radio and television stations nationwide. There are also a very small amount of miscellaneous files that appear to be from the desk of Alex Nogales. A portion of the file titles were enhanced or created by the processor.
Organization and Arrangement
Files in the collection are arranged alphabetically by file titles.
Mexican Americans on television -- Archives.; Mexican Americans in television broadcasting -- Archives.; Mexican Americans and television -- Archives.; Mexican Americans in the motion picture industry -- Archives.; Mexican Americans and mass media -- Archives.; National Hispanic Media Coalition -- Archives
- 10th anniversary notes - planning materials, (1996-1997) (Box 14, Folder 13)
- 1986 Annual Report of the Community Relations Servic published by the US Department of Justice (Box 26, Folder 19)
- 1988 Report on Television published by Nielsen Media Research, (1998) (Box 37, Folder 5)
- ABC Pollack meeting - NHMC/ABC agreement, minutes, correspondence, resumes, (1993) (Box 19, Folder 16)
  General note
  Includes EEO program report for KABC-TV, KGO-TV, and KFSN-TV.
- ABC/Disney - clippings, (1995-1996) (Box 33, Folder 1)
- ADL (Anti-Defamation League) - organization information, (1987) (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Adrianne Lara - Howard Stern complaint, (1995 April-May) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Advocacy Groups and the Entertainment Industry - conference materials, (1997 Feb) (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Agenda for unidentified meeting, (1995 Oct 30) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Airwaves Auction - clipping, (1994 Oct 26) (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Al Jerome /KCET - programming information, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Al Westcott - complaints about Howard Stern, (1997) (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Alicia Vega - letter to Robert Hoffman (Warner Bros.) - "Walking on Water", (1987 - 1988) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  Postcard from John F. Mendez - "Juarez".
- Alliance for Democracy - Disney sweat shops, (1997) (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Alliance Stations - handwritten list, (ca. 1995 Sept) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AMAE [Association of Mexican-American Educators] - contact information, (no date) (Box 23, Folder 6)
- American Arab Anti-Discrimination - national convention correspondence, (1997) (Box 10, Folder 7)
- American Asians - LA Times clipping, (1987 July 19) (Box 23, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), Los Angeles Local - survey of local news broadcasters' use of women and minorities, (no date) (Box 25, Folder 15)
- American Psychological Association - children and television advertising research, (1987) (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Amigos - Disney/ABC boycott - draft NHMC outreach letter, (1997 July 31) (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Angie Medina - Daily Variety clipping, (1996 Nov 22) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Anheuser-Busch - Howard Stern advertising and company downsizing letters, (1996-1997) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Anna Fisher - "Domestic violencegate" press release, (1997 Dec 30) (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Arab Americans - LA Times clipping, (1997 July 28) (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Armando Navarro - Affirmation Action Teach In press release, (1997 Nov 27) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Armando Valdez - position paper: Staking out the Public Interest in the Merger between Pacific Telesis and SBC, (1997 Feb) (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Arturo Montez - political letters, (1997 March, Oct) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Asian American Journalists Association - newsletters, (1988 Summer - Fall) (Box 37, Folder 10)
- AT&T - Al Dia con AT&T magazine, (1995 Fall) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Audio Cassettes - 17 items, (ca. 1990s) (Box 39)
  Restricted access: use of audio recordings may require production of listening copies. Includes: Messages KLSX; Stern - Comments of Selena; Selena: Joe Crummey KMPC; Xavier and Crummey KMPC; Xavier and Crummey KMPC; Bill Handel (KFI) on Selena; Roberto Arguello; Paul Rodriguez; Funeral Home for Hispanic - KRTH News; AEN.
- Augustin Martinez - KMEX TV financial pledge to NHMC, (1997 Aug 1) (Box 10, Folder 15)
- AztecaNet Website - company information and invoices, (1999 June) (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Back Stage West clipping, (1995 Feb 2) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bank of America/Rainbow - draft of settlement and related documents, (1993) (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Barbosa and Garcia - letter from Henry Barbosa to Councilman Robles re: Disney, (1998 Jan 20) (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Bel Hernandez - Latin Heat Seminar 95 mini tape cassette, (1995) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Restricted access: use of audio recordings may require production of listening copies.
- Belen Robles - ABC boycott, (1995-1997) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  With correspondence about issues between LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) and NHMC.
- Belen Robles - ABC boycott, (1995-1997) (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Belen Robles Media Kits - ABC boycott, (1995-1997) (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Ben Benavidez - MAPA (Mexican American Political Association) information packet, (1999 Sept 1) (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Benefactor Solicitations - NHMC's requests for financial support, (1987 June) (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Bert Corona - Hermandad Mexicana Nacional Legal Center - communication with Union Bank about funds, (1996 July) (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Betty Swinners - letter from Alex Nogales, (1996 March 14) (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Bill Richardson - fundraiser invite for Alex Nogales, (1996 June) (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Board of Supervisors - LA County denounce Howard Stern, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bob Dornan - clippings, ( ca. 1996) (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Bob Jimenez - correspondence - KCOP employment, (1997 Aug) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bob Morones - resume, (1996-1997) (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Bob Thompson - communication as NHMC's legal counsel, (ca. 1995-1996) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  With notice of Thompson's withdrawal as counsel.
- Buenas Noches America - fact sheet, (1995 Jan) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Business Women [Leadership Foundation] - National Summit snapshots, (1997) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- CA Wellness Foundation (The) - organization information, (1999 March 23) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  With 1998 annual report.
- CABE (California Association for Bilingual Education) - letter to Time Magazine, (1995 March 30) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- California State Advisory Committee to the US Commission on Civil Rights - forum on employment issues in the broadcast industry, (1994 Oct) (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Candy Saenz - resume, (1996 April 25) (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Carlos Ramirez - LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) request for NHMC support, (1995 May 31) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Fax date is June 1996.
- Carmen Avila - Hispanic Film Project update memo, (1997 April 23) (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Carol Urzi - correspondence - Bay Area radio stations, (1995 Jul-Oct) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Carole Black - thank you note, (1994 Sept 13) (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Catherine Suitor - Liberty Hill Foundation grant information, (1996) (Box 10, Folder 23)
- CBS - correspondence with NHMC about equal opportunity employment for Hispanics, (1987 - 1990) (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Cecilia Martinez - Family Theater Productions Advisory Committee - thank you, (1995 Aug) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Census current population reports - The Hispanic population in the US: March 1991 published by the US Department of Commerce, (1991 Oct) (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Center for Media and Public Affairs - Study: Blacks Outpace Hispanics in Primetime press release, (1987 Aug 5) (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Center for Media Literacy - organization information, (1997) (Box 10, Folder 24)
- CFPR (Committee for Fair Political Reporting) - press release, (1997 Aug 4) (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Chancellor Broadcasting - company financial data, (1996 Aug) (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Channel 22 - Alex Nogales FORO 22 appearance, (1996 Jan 25) (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Channel 22 Advertising - rates (for women) LA County Campaign, (1995 Aug) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Chapters Reports - NHMC South Texas and New York, (1999 Jan) (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Cheech Marin - legal declaration and scripts, ( ca. 1996) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  With scripts for: Hacienda Heights (The Dishwasher) and Valdez (Pilot).
- Chicago Latino Film Festival - program, (1997 April) (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Chicano Employees Association - press release - John Hill, Los Angeles County Affirmative Action Officer - lawsuit, (ca. 1995 Oct) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Children Now - special report titled Children Values and the Entertainment Media, (1995 June) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  May have been created by Alex Nogales.
- Children Now - special report titled: Children Watching Television: The Role of Advertisers -, (1996 July) (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Childrens Programming - FCC fact sheets and clippings, (1995 April and Sept) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- City of Los Angeles General Manager Department of Animal Regulation - eligible list of position candidates, (1993) (Box 20, Folder 11)
- City of Los Angeles, Commission on the Status of Women - women and AIDS campaign proposal guidelines, (1989) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  With Department of Communications job announcements.
- Civil rights act of 1990 - MALDEF (Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund) Hispanic leadership roundtable materials, (1990 March - April) (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Civil Rights Advisory Committee - testimonies from Alex Nogales, E.R., Armando Duron, (1993-1994) (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Classic Couriers - complaint against ABC, (ca. 1996) (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Clippings, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Clippings, (1994-1995) (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Clippings, (1986, 1988 - 1989) (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Coalition 93 license renewals - testimony of Esther Renteria to US Civil Rights Commission and Glass Ceilings commission, (1993-1994) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  With statistics about Latino employees at LA and NY television stations.
- Coalition for Hispanic Advancement - Merit Systems Protection Board (MSPB) Strategic Planning materials, (1997 Aug-Sept) (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Code of Ethics - NHMC policy, (no date) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Comite De Padres - flyer, (1995 Nov) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Commerce Committee - Variety clipping, (1995 March 24) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Commission for Social Justice - outreach letter to NHMC, (1996 June 19) (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Committee for Fair and Ethical Practices - LA Times protest flyers (faxed copies), (1997 Aug-Sept) (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Community meeting 9/28/87 - informational materials, (1987 Sept 28) (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Community Organizations - Tri-City Democrats newsletters, (1995 Jan, April) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Complaints - shared from community, (ca. 1995) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus - organization information, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Corporation for Public Broadcasting - annual report, (1987) (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Cory Aguirre - LULAC (League of United Latin American Citizens) outreach for project partnership, (1996 June 11) (Box 5, Folder 37)
- COSSMHO [National Coalition of Hispanic Health and Human Services Organization] - press release, (1997 July 25) (Box 11, Folder 6)
- CPB (Corporation fro Public Broadcasting) - Guide to volunteer and internship programs and facts/figures pamphlet, (1987-1989) (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Cristina - press kit, (ca. 1989) (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Cruz Bustamente - LA Times clippings, (1996 Nov) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cultural diversity in Primetime TV - FCC press releases, Hispanic organizations list, reports on women and minorities in TV, (1993-1994) (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Culture Clash - Bordertown press materials, (1999 April) (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Current populations report titled The Hispanic Population in the US: March 1986 and 1987 published by US Department of Commerce, (1988 Dec) (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Curtis Striker - LA Times clipping, (1996 Oct 3) (Box 5, Folder 38)
- DAD (Dallas Association for Decency) - memo KEGL radio, (1995 Sept 26) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Daily Variety clippings, (1989 April - March) (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Dallas Observer (The) - clipping, (1990 Aug 20) (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Dallas/Fort Worth region - NHMC outreach letters to Hispanic community organizations and region concerns, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Dana Parsons - clippings, (1997 March, May) (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Danamar Productions: The Golden Age of the Mexican Cinema - script and ephemera, (1989) (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Daniel Munoz - complaint about Disney/ABC, (1997 June 25) (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Daniel R. Chavez - resume, (no date) (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Dave Bautista - Latino statistics: education, health, census, etc., (no date) (Box 21, Folder 3)
- David Cruz - letters to Alex Nogales for development of radio talk show, (1996-1997) (Box 11, Folder 11)
- David Duron - resume, (ca. 1995) (Box 11, Folder 12)
- David Garcia - resume, (no date) (Box 11, Folder 13)
- David Hall - Arbitron rankings of LA radio stations, (1995, Fall 1994) (Box 21, Folder 2)
- David Honig - CA TV stations EEO performance report, (1993 July 19) (Box 21, Folder 4)
- David Tacovsky [Tokofsky] - LAUSD (Los Angeles Unified School District) Board Member communication about KLCS-TV, (ca. 1996) (Box 5, Folder 39)
- De La Rosa, Nancy - legal documents suit against State of Michigan, (1994-1995) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Dee Ortega - KVCR TV/FM, (1997-1998) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  With annual employment reports from 1988-1996.
- Del Zamora - LA Times clipping, (1996 May 20) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Demographics - Consulate General of Mexico - bulletin type flyers, (ca. 1995) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Denver region - Rocky Mountain News regional concern, (1987) (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Department of Justice - contact information, (no date) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- DGA Directory of Latino members - with information on Jesus Trevino, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dia de los Ninos - invitation for Esther Renteria to participate in event from National Latino Children's Institute, (1998 Nov 18) (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Diane Martinez - NHMC support for Assembly Bill AB 1206 (bilingual education funds), (1997 May) (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Diane Medina - correspondence - KABC and Hispanic staffing, (1995-1997) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Disappearing Latinos - material for board members about decrease of Latinos in television, (1999) (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Disney - clippings and press material, (1996-1998) (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Disney - NHMC's campaign against ABC/Disney, (1997 Aug-Oct) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  May contain duplicate letters in other ABC/Disney related files.
- Disney - NHMC's campaign against ABC/Disney, (1995-1997) (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Disney - NHMC's campaign against Disney [Alex Nogales file?], (1990-1998) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  With clippings about end of boycott.
- Disney buttons for anti-Disney campaign (8 items), (no date) (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Disney Financials - Disney generated financial reports [for stock holders?], (1997) (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Disney/ABC - clippings and photocopied letters, (1997) (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Disney/ABC [NHMC] strategies [towards boycott], (1997 March) (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Disney/ABC Discrimination, (1997 May) (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Disney/ABC/KCAL - FCC documents and photocopied letters, (1990-1997) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  May contain duplicate documents in other ABC/Disney related files.
- Disney/Petition to Deny License Renewals, (1996-1997) (Box 33, Folder 10)
  Contains duplicate materials found in other Disney/ABC related files.
- Disney/Young Appeal - initiated by NHMC - legal briefs, (1997 Oct) (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Disneyland Expansion, (1996 Sept-Oct) (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Dolores Sanchez - complaint about ABC/Disney, (ca. 1997) (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Don Ohlmeyer - clippings, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Donna Guerrero - Hispanic Women in Leadership conference information, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  With correspondence and clippings.
- Dornan vs. Sanchez Orange County election - clippings, press releases, letters, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- [Armando Duron's file?], (1989 - 1990) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  May have been created by Armando Duron.
- [Duron, Armando file?], (1989) (Box 27, Folder 1)
- [Duron, Armando file?] (1 of 2) - clippings and NHMC fact sheet, (1986-1989) (Box 37, Folder 16)
- [Duron, Armando file?] (2 of 2) - clippings and NHMC fact sheet, (1986-1989) (Box 37, Folder 17)
  Clippings only. May have been created by Armando Duron.
- Duron, Armando - handwritten notes, (1988 - 1989) (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Duron, Armando - LA Times clipping, (1995 June 19) (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Duron, Armando - notes and fax covers, (1994) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Dyana Ortelli - Frida Kahlo protest, (1994) (Box 23, Folder 38)
- E Channel -clipping, (ca. 1997) (Box 11, Folder 17)
- East Los Angeles College Campus news - clipping, (1989 April 12) (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Eastside Papers - clippings, (1994 June 16, 1998 April 30) (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Ed Baruch - Hispanic Film Project - planning materials, (1997) (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Eddie Navarro - response to complaint filed by Florida Board of Bar Examiners, (1997 April) (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Education celebration - letter from Mayor Bradley and two day event proposal, (1987 Nov 4) (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Educational Broadcasting Corporation - FCC renewal license materials, (1990) (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Edward L. Gonzales - FCC petition to deny transfer of control of KVDA- TV, (1989) (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Edward Vargas - biography, (no date) (Box 11, Folder 21)
- EEO (Equal Employment Opportunity) - FCC rules in broadcast radio and television services, (1987) (Box 24, Folder 10)
- EEO (Equal Employment Opportunity) and [license] renewal applications for television stations, (1998 July) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Includes KRCA, KTTV, KCAL, KSCI, KLCS, KCET, KWHY, KVEA.
- EEOC (Equal Employment Opportunity Commission) - clippings and letter requesting support, (ca. 1996) (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Elena Durazo - New Otani Hotel boycott flyer, (1996 Jan 24) (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Elizabeth Thomas - clipping, (1997 Oct 20) (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Employment outreach project data bank - list of Hispanic controlled radio/TV stations in California, (1988 July 19) (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Enchantment Artists - Valerie McCaffrey casting bulletin, (1996 Aug 26) (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Entertainment Law Digest - Sept issue, (1996) (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Entrepreneurs - clipping, (1995 Feb) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission - LA Times clipping, (1996 Feb 2) (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Equal Employment Opportunity in the Broadcast and Cable Industries - conference materials, (1989 Jan) (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Espinoza, Henry - seeking position with Disney, (1997 May) (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Esteban Torres - letters of support for Secretary of Labor, (1996 Dec 19) (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Esther NHMC 10th Anniversary - press releases, (1996 Nov) (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Esther Renteria's letter to Richard Schlosberg (LA Times), (1994 April 11) (Box 23, Folder 34)
- [Esther Renteria's file?] - letters, clippings, notes, and ephemera, (1988-1993) (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Family Perez - LA Times clippings for film The Perez Family, (1995 May) (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Father Santillan - protest against LA Times, (1997 July-Aug) (Box 11, Folder 23)
- FCC - Minority ownership survey (blank), (no date) (Box 24, Folder 11)
- FCC EEO Rules - replies from NAB (National Association of Broadcasters) and US West Communications, (1994 June 28) (Box 23, Folder 35)
- FCC First Report and Order - in the matter of Formulation of Policies and Rules Relating to Broadcast Renewal Applicants..., (1989 May 16) (Box 28, Folder 6)
- FCC information (All) - list of phone numbers, (no date) (Box 22, Folder 27)
- FCC memo opinion and order and notices of liability - KTKT/KLPX FM and WOR AM, (1994 April) (Box 23, Folder 36)
- FCC news bulletins, (1989 - 1990) (Box 24, Folder 12)
- FCC press release, (1994 June 29) (Box 23, Folder 37)
- FCC proposals to encourage minority and female ownership in telecommunications industry, (1994-1995) (Box 23, Folder 26)
- February 4 meeting - retreat agenda with clippings, (ca. 1994-1995) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Federico Subervi - resume, (1998) (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Fidel Vargas - MALDEF (Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund) banquet - letter, (1995 Nov) (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Filemon Vela, Jr. - letter to NHMC about Gallo Wine vs. Joe Lopez, (1997 Feb 5) (Box 11, Folder 24)
- First Amendment - Newton Minow's book - clipping, (1995 Sept 16) (Box 1, Folder 29)